Jerome Kern Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-95, Box 103-116)
  - Manuscripts (Box 1-94, Box 103-116)
    - Show Boat (1927) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - No Mason Dixon Line, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 58 p.; Note: this number was dropped during pre-Broadway tryout, also titled "It's getting hotter in the North" (Box-folder 56/7)
      - [Ol' man river], Holograph sketch in ink over pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 58/17)
      - Ol' man river, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 6 p. (Box-folder 58/18)
      - Ol' man river: #3: [in B], Parts (Box-folder 63/7)
      - Ol' man river: #3: [in C], Parts (Box-folder 64/1)
      - Reprise ol' man river: #33: [in B], Parts; Uniform title: Ol' man river (Box-folder 64/2)
      - Reprise ol' man river: #33: [in D and Db], Parts, 2 sets; Uniform title: Ol' man river (Box-folder 64/3)
      - Opening act I scene I, Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in pencil and ink, some dummy lyrics by Kern; 16 p. + [4] p. laid in (Box-folder 58/19)
      - Opening act I scene III: waterfront saloon, Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 58/20)
      - Opening act II, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 60 p. (Box-folder 56/8)
      - New opening act II, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 4 p.; Uniform title: Opening act 2 (Box-folder 56/9)
      - Opening act II, Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink; [12] p.; Note: this is not the version used in the show (Box-folder 58/21)
      - Opening act II: #19, Parts (Box-folder 64/4)
      - Incidental opening act II: #19a, Parts; Uniform title: Opening act 2: incidental (Box-folder 64/5)
      - Opening chorus, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in Kern's hand in pencil; 131 p.; Includes "Make believe" (p. 99) (Box-folder 56/10, Box-folder 57/1)
      - Opening chorus: part I: #1, Parts (Box-folder 64/6)
      - Opening chos.: part II: #2, Parts (Box-folder 65/1)
      - Opening final scene: #35a, Parts (Box-folder 65/2)
      - Opening pantry scene, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-5, A-G; Note: segues directly into "Can't help lovin' dat man"; Note: crossed out full score material on back of p. A-G, titled "Magnolia and Julie continue" (Box-folder 57/2)
      - Opening pantry scene: Act I scene II., Holograph piano score in ink; [3] p. (Box-folder 58/22)
      - Opening pantry scene: #4, Parts (Box-folder 65/3)
      - Opening scene: #6, Parts (Box-folder 65/4)
      - Opening trocadero: act II scene VI, Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink; [6] p. (Box-folder 58/23)
      - Opening trocadero: act II scene VI, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; [1] p. (incomplete) (Box-folder 58/23)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 31 p. (Box-folder 57/3)
      - Overture, Parts (Box-folder 65/5)
      - [Queenies ballyhoo], Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink; [3] p. (Box-folder 58/24)
      - Queenie's dance: #14a, Parts (Box-folder 65/6)
      - Queenie's outburst, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 30 p.; Note: a.k.a. "Queenie's ballyhoo" or "C'mon folks" (Box-folder 57/4)
      - Queenie's outburst: #14, Parts (Box-folder 66/1)
      - Rehearsal scene -- N1: #10, Parts (Box-folder 66/2)
      - Rehearsal scene -- N2: #10a, Parts; Note: for horn and trumpet parts see "Rehearsal scene - N1" (Box-folder 66/3)
      - Sammy White, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 10 p. (Box-folder 57/5)
      - Sammy White: #'s 15, 15a, Parts (Box-folder 66/4)
      - Scena: Magnolia and Julie: act I scene II See also: "Magnolia and Julie", Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink, partial lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 58/25)
      - Scena: Magnolia and Julie, Ms. (Robert R. Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric mostly in Kern's hand; 8 p.; Note: both mss. for this cut scene include reprises of "Make believe," one with a different lyric and incomplete (Box-folder 58/26)
      - Scena Magnolia & Julie: act I scene II, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, lyric (by copyist, Hammerstein and Kern), in pencil, unfinished; 8 p. (Box-folder 58/26)
      - Scena [water-barrel]: act I scene VII, Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink, no lyric; 4 p. (Box-folder 59/1)
      - Scena (water-barrel), Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, lyrics in pencil; 10 p.; Note: alternate titles: "Creole love song," "Remembering you," "Wanting you" (Box-folder 59/1)
      - Terzetto, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; [30] p.; Includes: "I might fall back on you" (Box-folder 57/6)
      - Terzett[o]: Capt. Magnolia & Parthy, Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p.; Note: refrain became "I might fall back on you" (Box-folder 59/2)
      - There'll be a hot time in the old town tonight see: Hot time in the old town tonight
      - 'Till good luck comes my way see: Waterfront saloon
      - ['Till good luck comes my way], Holograph sketch in ink; [3] p. (Box-folder 59/3)
      - Trocadero cake walk: #26, Parts (Box-folder 66/5)
      - Villain's dance, Flute part only (Box-folder 66/6)
      - *Washington Post march: #'s 24, 29, Parts; Music by John Philip Sousa (Box-folder 66/7)
      - Wasserman part III: #11, Parts (Box-folder 66/8)
      - Waterfront saloon; ['Till] good luck comes my way, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-11, 1-21 (Box-folder 57/7)
      - Waterfront saloon: #9, Parts (Box-folder 66/9)
      - Why [do I love you]?, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 31 p. + 2nd p. 31 (Box-folder 57/8)
      - Why do I love you?, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 59/4)
      - Why do I love you?: #20, Parts (Box-folder 67/1)
      - Yes m'am!: Elly and boys: scene III act I, Photocopy of holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink, no lyric; 5 p.; Note: became "First mate Martin" in Sweet Adeline (Box-folder 59/5)
      - You are love, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink and pencil; 42 p. (incomplete); Note: on back of p. 41 are 2 measures that could serve as an ending to p. 40 (Box-folder 57/9)
      - You are love: Water-barrel scene, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 7 p. (Box-folder 59/6)
      - You are love: #13, Parts (Box-folder 67/2)
      - You are love: #16, Parts (Box-folder 67/3)
      - You are love reprise: #35: [in Eb], Parts (Box-folder 67/4)
      - You are love reprise: #35: [in F], Parts (Box-folder 67/5)
      - [Miscellaneous full scores], Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; [6] p.; Includes: "Rejected pages/Opening act II" "Rejected p. 21 + 22/Rehearsal #7/ 'Lover's part'" "Scena: Magnolia and Julie" (Box-folder 57/10)
      - [Miscellaneous Kern sketches]: [Untitled]: notes for R.R.B., Holograph sketches in ink; [2] p.; Includes headings: "Scene V Act II. Frank does this version to show Nola how to land a job." "Segue 1st Verse and Refrain 'Can't Help Lovin' dat Man' Act I Scene " (Box-folder 59/7)
      - [Miscellaneous Kern sketches]: [Unidentified], Holograph sketches in ink; [2] p.; Includes: "Frank & Elly dance" ms. in pencil, crossed out (Box-folder 59/7)
      - [Miscelaneous piano-vocal scores], Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal scores in ink, most with no lyrics; p. [1], 3-4, 3-6, 19-20; Note: p. [1] melody only; titled "before Lady Luck" (Box-folder 59/8)
      - [Material for preparation of published piano-vocal score]: Overture, Ms. (mostly Leonid Raab) piano score in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 59/9)
      - [Material for preparation of published piano-vocal score]: Opening; Captain Andy's ballyhoo; Who cares if my boat goes upstream, Ms. (mostly Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, annotations by Bennett, Kern and others; p. 9-14, [7]-44; Includes: "Captain Andy's ballyhoo" "Who cares if my boat goes upstream?" "Make believe" (Box-folder 59/9)
      - [Material for preparation of published piano-vocal score]: Ol' man river, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 59/9)
      - [Material for preparation of published piano-vocal score]: Scene II. Kitchen pantry of the "Cotton Blossom": introduction and opening, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 59/9)
      - [Material for preparation of published piano-vocal score]: Can't help loving that man, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink with inserts from printed score; p. 4-21 (Box-folder 59/9)
      - [Material for preparation of published piano-vocal score]: Scene III. Outside a waterfront saloon: opening, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 2 p.; Note: includes [.5] p. attachment to complete the end. (Box-folder 59/9)
      - Show Boat selection, Ms. (arranged by Hans Spialek) piano score in ink; p. 1-9, 9a, 10-15 (Box-folder 59/10)
      - Show Boat selection, Ms. (compiled and arranged by Victor Baravalle) piano score in ink, includes pasteovers from printed score; 17 p. (Box-folder 59/10)
      - Show Boat selection, Ms. (arranged by Stephen O. Jones) piano score in pencil, includes pages laid in from the printed score with annotations in pencil; 27 p. (Box-folder 59/10)
      - Show Boat: grande valse, Ms. piano score in ink; [8] p. (Box-folder 59/11)
      - [Harp parts], Parts (Box-folder 67/6)
      - [Unidentified violin parts], Parts (Box-folder 67/7)
      - [Partial script and lyric sheet]: Act I [scene 1], Typed script, annotations by Kern in pencil; p. [1]-26 (Box-folder 59/12)
      - [Partial script and lyric sheet]: Scene five, Typed script, annotations by Kern in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 59/12)
      - [Partial script and lyric sheet]: Bill, Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 59/12)
      - [Show Boat souvenir program]: Ziegfeld theatre, Printed program for New York opening with annotations in pencil; [38] p. (Box-folder 59/13)
      - Musical program, Ms. (probably Charles Miller) contents list for printed piano-vocal score, in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 59/14)
    - The Siren (1911) lyric by Matthew Woodward
      - My heart I cannot give to you, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, signature and title by Kern; [3] p.; Typed lyric sheet, annotations in red ink; [2] p. (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Sitting Pretty (1924) lyrics by P.G. Wodehouse
      - All the world is dancing mad, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 33 p. (Box-folder 68/2)
      - All you need is a girl!, Arranger's holograph (Max Steiner) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 22 p. (Box-folder 68/3)
      - All you need is a girl: duettino -- Bill and May, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p.; Typed lyric sheet laid in; [1] p. (Box-folder 71/1)
      - Ballet; Shadow of the moon: score II, Arranger's holograph (Max Steiner and Charles Miller?) full score in ink, annotations in red ink; p. 1-14, 11-16, 21-22, 25-26; Note: drawn from "Shadow of the moon," "Mr. & Mrs. Rorer" et al. (Box-folder 68/4)
      - Bongo on the Congo, Arranger's holograph (Max Steiner) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 13 p. + [2] p. of notes (Box-folder 68/5)
      - Bongo [on the Congo], Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 71/2)
      - Bongo [on the Congo], Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil by P.G. Wodehouse; [4] p. (Box-folder 71/2)
      - Bongo on the Congo: trio: Judson -- Jo -- Horace, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, 2nd lyric in red pencil; 5 p.; Typed lyric sheet laid in; 3 p. (Box-folder 71/2)
      - Dear old fashioned prison of mine see: Prison of mine see: Tulip time in Sing Sing
      - Desert island, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotations by Max Steiner; 22 p. (Box-folder 68/6)
      - Desert island, Holograph sketch in pencil; 2 p. (Box-folder 71/3)
      - On a desert island with you, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink and red pencil; [5] p. (Box-folder 71/3)
      - On a desert island with you, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 71/3)
      - [The enchanted train]: Duettino, Holograph sketch in pencil; 2 p. (Box-folder 71/4)
      - The enchanted train, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 71/4)
      - The enchanted train See also: "The magic train", Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil and incomplete lyric, some in Kern's hand; [10] p.; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 71/4)
      - Exit march, Ms. full score in ink, annotations by Max Steiner; 8 p. (Box-folder 68/7)
      - Finale ultimo, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; [1] p. (incomplete) (Box-folder 68/8)
      - Unused piano part of finale, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, some pencil lyrics in Kerns hand; p. 17-18, 21-27; Uniform title: Finale (Box-folder 71/5)
      - Finaletto, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotations by Max Steiner; p. 1-48, 39-57, + [1] p. laid in (Box-folder 68/9)
      - Finaletto act I, Photocopy of holograph sketch; 10 p. (Box-folder 71/6)
      - I'd want only you, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 21 p.; Note: dropped before New York opening; a.k.a. "You alone would do" (Box-folder 68/10)
      - I'd want only you: You alone would do, Holograph sketch in pencil; 1 p. (Box-folder 71/7)
      - I'm wise, Arranger's holograph (Hilding Anderson) full score in ink; 21 p. (Box-folder 68/11)
      - Interlude, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 11 p. (incomplete) (Box-folder 68/12)
      - Just wait see: Some girl will get you
      - Mr. and Mrs. Rorer, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotations by Max Steiner; p. 1-24, 26-34 (Box-folder 68/13)
      - Mr. & Mrs. Rorer, Holograph sketch in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 71/8)
      - Mr. and Mrs. Rorer, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 71/8)
      - The magic train, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink with corrections by Max Steiner; p. 1-24 (p. 5-11, 17-24 are photocopies); Note: originals of the photocopied pages are in "Overture" (Box-folder 69/1)
      - 2nd encore (magic train) See also: "The enchanted train", Arranger's holograph (Max Steiner) full score in ink; 8 p. (Box-folder 69/1)
      - On a desert island with you see: Desert island
      - Opening B, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 46 p.; Note: this is the original "Opening," comprising "Scene music," "Roses are nodding" and "Coaching" (Box-folder 69/2)
      - Opening B, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) sketch in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 71/9)
      - Opening act I, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations and partial lyric in pencil in Kern's hand; p. 1-4, 9-16 (Box-folder 71/9)
      - Opening scene act II, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 44 p. (Box-folder 69/3)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotations by Max Steiner; p. 1-12, 5-11, 13-18, 17-28, 58-59 [39 p. total] (Box-folder 69/4)
      - Prison of mine, Arranger's holograph (Hilding Anderson) full score in ink, annotaitons by Max Steiner; 9 p.; Note: a.k.a. "Tulip time in Sing Sing" or "Dear old fashioned prison of mine" (Box-folder 69/5)
      - Prison of mine, Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 71/10)
      - Queenie's number, Arranger's holograph (R. R. Bennett) full score and Hilding Anderson insert (heavily crossed out) in ink, annotations by Max Steiner; p. 1-23, 23A-23D, 24-31; Note: uses the same music as "Shadow of the moon" (Box-folder 69/6)
      - Shadow of the moon See also: "Ballet" See also: "Queenie's number", Ms. full score in ink; 31 p.; Note: for Dolly Sisters' post-Broadway tour (Box-folder 69/7)
      - Shadow of the moon, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 6 p.; Typed lyric sheet laid in; [1] p. (Box-folder 71/11)
      - Shufflin' Sam, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotations by Max Steiner; 34 p. (Box-folder 69/8)
      - Shufflin' Sam; Encore -- Shufflin' Sam, Ms. full score in ink; 36 p.; Note: for Dolly Sisters' post-Broadway tour (Box-folder 69/9)
      - Shufflin' Sam, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [5] p.; Typed lyric sheet laid in; [1] p. (Box-folder 71/12)
      - Sitting pretty, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 23 p.; Note: cut before New York opening (Box-folder 69/10)
      - Sitting pretty, Holograph sketch in pencil, including the original lyric for burthen; 2 p. (Box-folder 71/13)
      - Sitting pretty, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [7] p.; Typed lyric sheet laid in; [1] p.; Note: the holograph is different from the final version of the song (Box-folder 71/13)
      - Some girl will get you, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p.; Note: a.k.a. "Just wait" and cut before New York opening (Box-folder 70/1)
      - Ten nights in a ball room see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - One girl who believes, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotations by Max Steiner; p. 1-12, 12-16; Uniform title: There isn't one girl (Box-folder 70/2)
      - 2nd encore: I act 7a, Arranger's holograph (Max Steiner) full score in ink; 9 p.; Uniform title: There isn't one girl (Box-folder 70/2)
      - [There isn't] one girl, Ms. full score in ink; 15 p.; Note: for Dolly Sisters' post-Broadway tour (Box-folder 70/3)
      - Troubles in a box See also: "Worries", Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 71/14)
      - Tulip time in Sing Sing See also: "Prison of mine", Ms. full score in ink; 10 p.; Note: for Dolly Sisters' post-Broadway tour. (Box-folder 70/4)
      - Tulip time in Sing Sing, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in red pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 71/15)
      - Tulip time [in Sing Sing], Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 71/15)
      - Valse, Arranger's holograph (probably Emil Gerstenberger) full score in ink; 7 p. (Box-folder 70/5)
      - Worries; Pick up for "Worries" encore, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotaitons by Max Steiner; 28 p. + [1] p. (Box-folder 70/6)
      - Worries, Ms. full score in ink; 28 p.; Note: for Dolly Sisters' post-Broadway tour (Box-folder 70/7)
      - Worries See also: "Troubles in a box", Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p.; Typed lyric sheet laid in; [1] p. (Box-folder 71/16)
      - Worries See also: "Troubles in a box", Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 71/16)
      - A year from today, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink, annotations by Max Steiner; 12 p. (Box-folder 70/8)
      - A year from today, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink and red pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 71/17)
      - A year from today, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 5 p.; Typed lyric sheet laid in; [1] p. (Box-folder 71/17)
      - You alone would do see: I'd want only you
      - Sitting Pretty selection, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in pencil with annotated pages from printed piano-vocal scores; 22 p.; Includes: "Worries" "A year from today" "Bongo on the Congo" "Shufflin' Sam" "The enchanted train" "All you need is a girl" "Shadow of the moon" "Mr. and Mrs. Rorer" (Box-folder 71/18)
      - [Unidentified holograph]: tempo cor ang lazy [sic], Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p.; On back: crossed out cue sheet in Bennett and Kern's hands in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 71/19)
      - [Miscellaneous parts], Parts (Box-folder 71/20)
    - The Spring Chicken (1906)
      - Gwendoline of Grosvenor square, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; 10 p.; Note: dated 1912 (subsequent to the show) (Box-folder 71/21)
    - Stepping Stones (1923) lyrics by Anne Caldwell
      - [Babbling Babette], Holograph sketch in pencil; 2 p. (Box-folder 72/1)
      - Opening of scene, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; [4] p. (Box-folder 72/1)
      - [Because you love the singer]: Trio (Loupina, Captain, DeWolfe), Holograph sketch in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 72/2)
      - Cane dance: act II, Holograph sketch in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 72/3)
      - Cane dance encore, Arranger's holograph (Hilding Anderson) full score in ink; 7 p. (Box-folder 72/4)
      - The clock: opening act I, Holograph piano score/sketch in pencil, last 3 measures missing; 3 p. (Box-folder 72/5)
      - The clock: opening act I, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 2 p.; Note: also titled "The nursery clock" (Box-folder 72/5)
      - DeWolfe's entrance, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 72/6)
      - DeWolfe's entrance, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 72/6)
      - Dear little Peter Pan, Holograph sketch in pencil; 4 p. (different sizes) (Box-folder 72/7)
      - Dear little Peter Pan, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink, annotations in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 72/7)
      - Peter Pan, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 7 p.; Uniform title: Dear little Peter Pan (Box-folder 72/7)
      - Girl's entrance See also: "Little Red Riding Hood", Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 4 p.; Ms. outline for musical routine in pencil laid in; [1] p. (Box-folder 72/8)
      - Growing men, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 2 p. (Box-folder 72/9)
      - Growing men, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; [3] p. (Box-folder 72/9)
      - Hand in hand: act II, Holograph sketch in pencil; 2 p.; Note: this is an earlier title for "Stepping stones" (Box-folder 72/10)
      - I feel so sorry for the rose, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 72/11)
      - I saw the roses and remembered you, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal scores (6) in ink, in 5 keys; [27] p.; Lyric by Herbert Reynolds (Box-folder 72/12)
      - In love with love: Walking song, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; [2] p.; On cover: outline for musical routine in ink (Box-folder 72/13)
      - In love with love, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations and lyric in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 72/13)
      - Last number, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 72/14)
      - [Last number]: Energetico, Holograph sketch in pencil; 2 p. (Box-folder 72/14)
      - Little angel cake, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 2 p.; On cover: outline for musical routine in ink (Box-folder 72/15)
      - [Little angel cake]: Intro (Steve's mss.), Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 72/15)
      - [Little angel cake], Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; p. 3-4 (Box-folder 72/15)
      - Little Red Riding Hood, or, Everybody calls me Little Red Riding Hood See also: "Girl's entrance", Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; [2] p.; On cover: outline for musical routine in ink (Box-folder 72/16)
      - Little Red Riding Hood, or, Everybody calls me Little Red Riding Hood See also: "Girl's entrance", Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 72/16)
      - [Little Red Riding Hood entrance]: Slow gavotte, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) sketch in pencil, annotations by Kern; [2] p. (Box-folder 72/17)
      - [Once in a blue moon]: Song: Prince and girls, Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 72/18)
      - [Once in a blue moon]: Song: Prince and girls, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 2 p.; On cover: outline for musical routine in ink (Box-folder 72/18)